letsprogram.com 2014-06-03

# Privacy Policy | Let's program

**Personal Information:**  
Letsprogram.com does not request or collect any personal information about you when you visit this web site. However, your Internet domain and IP address, the date and time you access the site, the pages you visit, and the type of browser and operating system you use are automatically collected and stored by the server the site is running on for the sole purpose of tracking the number and type of visitors using the site.

**Links to Other Sites:**  
This site contains links to other sites which is not controlled or owned by us. If you are no longer on our site, you are subject to the privacy policy on the new site.

**Third-Party Advertising and Cookies:**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this web site. These companies may collect information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to analyze the effectiveness of their ad campaigns and to provide advertisements for this web site and other web sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In order to monitor such statistics, a unique “cookie” is automatically generated and placed into your browser.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

  *   *
